Guide to the Philip Wagner papers, (ca. 1934-1997)
Wagner, Philip papers, (ca. 1934-1997)
- Series V. Photographs
  - 2 figures for Amerine book on wine making, n.d., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Wine judging and tasting (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Photos of vineyard, cellar, equipment, Philip Wagner, one labeled Maryland 1960. Photos came from Bully Hill / Taylor family. (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Boordy: Grape Exhibit and Photograph of Unknown Woman (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - August Mencken 1966 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Series VI. Newspaper Columns
  - Oversize print of Philip judging wine (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Three mounted sketches for advertisements (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Certificate of appointment to Wine Judging Committee of California State Agricultural Society for Philip, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Certificates of appointment of Philip and Jocelyn as wine judges in state of California, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Mounted clipping from THE SUN re wines in Maryland, n.d., 1950, 1963, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Photocopy of an article from the Evening Sun, Baltimore, titled Science on the Farm by PhilipWagner. September 24, 1937 (Box 17)
  - Scrapbooks of columns by Philip Wagner while on assignment in London, 1936-1937 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Series VII. Miscellaneous Publications
  - The Green Hoe Co., Inc., 1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - French Wines/Winery Brochures (Box 18, Folder 2-2A)
  - Various Machinery Brochures (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural Chemical Brochures (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Journal Articles, 1940-1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Alcohol Regulation Information 1979-1981 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Nursery Brochures and Grape Catalogues (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Progress Reports 1962-1964 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Maps and Map Catalogues (Box 18, Folder 9-10)
  - Philip Wagner's Publications (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Harper's Press Articles and Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Data Sheets, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Index Cards of Grape Varieties, Little Box (Box 18)